

DMITRY KHILIUK FRONT-END DEVELOPER

+375 29 5244578

khiliukbrest@gmail.com

Belarus, Brest











ABOUT ME

I'm frontend developer with experience in creating SPA using React, Redux, TypeScript, SCSS. I'm planning to study Node.is, because in the future i see myself as a Full-stack developer. Usualy i prefer to spend my leisure time on improving my English, studying new technologies and solve tasks on Codewars. Ready to consider project work and full-time employment . Also ready to consider moving.

EXPERIENCE

Freelance

(2021 - Present)

front-end developer

Use next deleloper technologies: React/Redux / ReduxToolkit/RestApi/Axios/StoryBook/Formik /MaterialUI/SCSS, etc. Check the correctness of the code with Unit Tests and take Storybook for demonstration of individual modules application. Use TypeScript for best control of the code in work.

Belorusneft

(2010 - 2021)

supervisor of the oil storage

- people management
- international transportation
- records management

BrestDorProject

(2005-2010)

structural engineer

- project development
- work with customers
- project coordination
- teamwork

SKILLS



HTML



CSS



JavaScript



TypeScript





Redux



REST API



Axios



GitHub



Heroku





StoryBook





LANGUAGE

English Pre-Intermedian (in progress)

EDUCATION

Brest State Technical University (2001 - 2006)

structural engineer

IT-INCUBATOR, 2021

frontend developer